That salute
Durgabai share market waale sahab like share
market mein bharti kahani today's preparation for tomorrow's market
this is a special video as I have
recorded earlier also, in the beginning
I have added one more share
with Zindagi and after Zindagi also ICICI
Lombard and HDFC Life along with that
you can also add SBI Life Insurance, all these
three shares are strong but among these shares
ICICI Lombard has more power
and I believe that if you have that much
strength that you
can go till 1836 in the West these days, the price has the
power to be long times team but there is a problem of a
subscribe accident,
inch Rohit subscribe and
but remember if
you go with this you will
get very good benefits and you will
get high rates, share market waale Shyam
Bhai, instead of buying in the share market
today's preparation 29th August 2002